melbourne.co.uk 2018-05-16

# Privacy Policy

## Below is a copy of our current Privacy Policy.

Melbourne Server Hosting Limited (“We” “Our”) considers the protection of your (“You”) privacy to be of utmost importance. We maintain strict customer information privacy policies and use state of the art technologies to safeguard customer information and communications from unauthorised intrusions and access.

As leading exponents in the fields of Managed Hosting and Data Centre Services, we recognise and understand that the growth of online services, including internet ecommerce services, has created additional privacy concerns, particularly around identify theft. This policy explains how we may collect information about you and then how we use it. It also gives certain assurances on things that we will and what we will not do.

## 1. Collection of Information

We may collect personal information about you when:

you take a service or product from us  
you contact us with an enquiry or in response to a communication from us  
We may take this information from you in a number of ways:

Internet & email  
Telephone (both fixed and mobile)  
Fax  
Text message or similar multimedia messaging application

## 2. Use of Information

2.1 Information you provide or we hold about you may be used by us and/or our agents to:

identify and respond to you when you make direct enquiries or requests to us  
administer any accounts, services and products provided by us  
undertake marketing & customer analysis  
help prevent and detect fraud or loss  
contact you about other services and products offered by us, and selected partners (provided you have given us prior consent)

## 3. Disclosure of Information

3.1. We may disclose information we hold about you to third parties for the purpose of providing services you have requested, as part of the process of sale, or where legitimately requested for legal or regulatory purposes, as part of legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings.

3.2. We will not sell, rent or share your personal information, with or to any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission.

## 4. Monitoring

We may monitor and record calls made to us for the purposes of quality assurance, legal, regulatory and training.

## 5. Protection of Information

We maintain strict security measures in order to protect personal information. These measures include technical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure, loss, alteration, or destruction. Credit card information is transmitted using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption.

## 6. Links to 3rd Party Web Sites.

Our website may contain links to other recognised and respected organisations websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on Melbourne Server Hosting Limited websites.

## 7. Transferring Data Outside of The UK

It may be necessary for us, in the normal course of our business, to transfer your personal information to other companies located in countries outside of the UK e.g. domain name hosts. You should note that the Data Protection laws and policies of these countries may not be as robust as the UK.

## 8. Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time and updated version will be posted on Melbourne Server Hosting Limited websites from time to time. Your continued use of our sites following the posting of changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the terms of the policy that applied at the time the information was collected.

## 9. Contact Us

If you would like further information about this policy or you wish to enquire about the data we hold about you, please contact us:

Melbourne Server Hosting Limited

Lovell House

Archway

Manchester

M15 5RN
